Guide to the Whirley Family Papers, 1853-1998 and undated RL.11315
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
Whirley family papers
1853-1998 and undated
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
Whirley family
RL.11315
25.4 Linear Feet
Carl and Enid Whirley were Southern Baptist missionaries in Nigeria from 1947 to 1980. The Whirley Family Papers includes material from throughout their lives, beginning with Carl's studies at Howard College, now Samford University, in the 1940s and ending with his and Enid's retirement into the 1990s. Their papers include correspondence, documents and photographs from the Whirleys' time in multiple regions of Nigeria, as well as Carl's sermon notes and teaching materials. Also includes printed materials from their time as missionaries, including Nigerian newspapers and clippings, church bulletins, and other articles, books, serials, pamphlets, and newsletters.
Arrangement
The colleciton initially arrived unsorted and has been sorted into six series: Teaching Materials, Speeches and Sermons, Correspondence, Nigerian Mission, Printed Materials, Personal Materials, and Audiovisual Materials.
Biographical / Historical
Carl and Enid Whirley were Southern Baptist missionaries to Nigeria from 1947 to 1980. In 1943 both graduated from Howard College, now Samford University, in Birmingham, Alabama. Carl completed a Doctor of Theology from the Southern Baptist Theological Seminary while in Nigeria in 1958. Enid completed the Woman's Missionary Union Training School. They began their time as missionaries at the Olivet Baptist High School, then called the Oyo Baptist Boys' High School, in 1948. Carl served as the school's principal. Thereafter they worked at the Baptist College in Iwo, Hillcrest School in Jos, and Newton Memorial School in Osogbo. From 1971-1979, Carl was president of the Nigerian Baptist Theological Seminary in Ogbomosho. Enid continued to remain active in the Women's Missionary Union of Nigeria. Upon retirement, Carl served as a professor in the religion department at Samford University until 1987. The Whirleys also returned to the United States on several occasions during their time as missionaries, during which they spoke at churches throughout the American South.
Access Restrictions
Collection is open for research.
Researchers must register and agree to copyright and privacy laws before using this collection.
All or portions of this collection may be housed off-site in Duke University's Library Service Center. The library may require up to 48 hours to retrieve these materials for research use.
Please contact Research Services staff before visiting the David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library to use this collection.
Provenance
The Whirley Family Papers were received by the David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library as a gift in 2016 and 2017.
Related Materials
Logan Family Papers, 1952-1994; McGee Family Papers, 1857-2013; Pool Family Papers, 1930-2000; Roberson Family Papers, 1917-1977; Loy Connell Smith and Eunice Andrews Smith Bland papers, 1958-1999; Taylor family papers, 1850-1975
Collection Overview
The Whirley Family Papers collection is divided into seven series: Teaching Materials, Speeches and Sermons, Correspondence, Nigerian Mission, Printed Materials, Personal Materials, and Audiovisual Materials. Teaching Materials is divided into four subseries: subject files, specific course materials, Samford University administration, and Carl Whirley's personal coursework and notes. Speeches and Sermons contains three subseries: Carl Whirley's sermon notes, sermons by himself and others, and speeches by himself and others. Correspondence contains contact between Carl and Enid with personal friends as well as American churches and official organizations. Nigerian Mission includes both administrative documents from various Nigerian missionary organizations as well as some uncaptioned photographs. Printed Materials consists of eight subseries: articles, newsletters, newspapers, pamphlets, serials, books, programs, and church bulletins, mostly from their time in Nigeria. Personal Materials largely relates to the lives both before and after their missionary work in Nigeria.
Yoruba (African people) -- Nigeria -- History; Nigeria -- History -- 20th century; Baptists -- Missions -- Nigeria; Baptists -- United States.; Birmingham (Ala.) -- Social life and customs; Missionaries -- Africa, West; Missionaries -- Correspondence; Southern Baptist Convention. Foreign Mission Board; Samford University; Whirley, Enid Pate; Whirley, Carl F., 1914-2000; American Baptist Missionary Union; Nigerian Baptist Theological Seminary, Ogbomoso
- Teaching Materials, 1944-1993 and undated
  Scope and Contents
  Teaching Materials consists of subject files, specific course materials, administrative documents, and Carl Whirley's personal coursework notes. Subject files include lecture notes on various world religions and books of the Bible, especially the New Testament. Course materials are specific to courses Carl taught while at Samford University from 1979-1987, and other institutions until 1990, including New Testament Survey and Comparative Religions. They include lecture notes, handouts, syllabi, exams, and student work samples. There is one folder of K-6 teaching material on Nigeria. Administrative documents are also from his time at Samford University. Whirley's personal coursework notes span 1944-1953. Arranged alphabetically by folder title within each sub-series.
  - Subject Files, 1945-1993 and undated; 1
    - Ancient American Religions, undated (Box 1)
      Carl Whirley lecture notes
    - Bahai, 1950s-1980s (Box 1)
      Carl Whirley lecture notes, handouts
    - Black Muslims, undated (Box 1)
      Handouts, pamphlets
    - Buddhism, 1979 (Box 1)
    - Christian Science, 1980s; 2 folders (Box 1)
      Carl Whirley lecture notes, handouts, pamphlets
    - Confucianism, undated (Box 1)
    - Gnosticism, 1980 (Box 1)
      Handout
    - Greek Orthodox Church, undated (Box 1)
      Pamphlet
    - Hinduism, undated (Box 1)
      Dr. Thomas Starkes's Tape: lecture notes, handouts
    - Islam, undated (Box 1)
    - Jainism, undated (Box 1)
    - Jehovah's Witnesses, 1983 and undated; 2 folders (Box 1)
      Carl Whirley lecture notes, handouts, Pamphlets, Religious literature
    - Judaism, undated (Box 1)
      Carl Whirley lecture notes, pamphlets, religious literature
    - Krishnas, 1983-1984 (Box 1)
      Carl Whirley lecture notes, serials
    - Literacy Missions, 1988-1989 and undated (Box 17, Folder 1)
      Handouts and pamphlet
    - Roy Lockhardt, 1980s (Box 1)
      Carl Whirley lecture notes, writings, clippings
    - Mormonism, 1980s; 3 folders (Box 1)
      Carl Whirley lecture notes, handouts, religious literature
    - Native Chinese Religion and Taoism, undated (Box 1)
    - Pluralism, 1983 (Box 1)
      Carl Whirley lecture notes, newspaper
    - Reincarnation, undated (Box 1)
      Carl Whirley lecture notes, religious literature
    - Religion in Prehistoric and Primative Cultures, undated (Box 1)
    - Seventh-Day Adventists, undated (Box 1)
      Carl Whirley lecture notes, handouts, religious literature, student work
    - Shintoism, 1980 (Box 1)
      Carl Whirley lecture Notes
    - Sikhism, undated (Box 1)
    - Theosophic Society, undated (Box 1)
    - Unification Church, undated (Box 1)
    - The Way International, undated (Box 1)
      Carl Whirley lecture notes, student work
    - Worldwide Church of God, 1982 (Box 1)
    - Zen Buddhism, undated (Box 1)
      Carl Whirley Lecture notes, religious literature
    - Zoroastrianism, undated (Box 1)
    - Genesis, 1970 (Box 2)
    - Exodus, undated (Box 2)
    - Psalms, 1945 (Box 2)
    - Isaiah, 1940s (Box 2)
    - Jeremiah, undated (Box 2)
    - Haggai, Zachariah, and Malachi, undated (Box 2)
    - Matthew, Gospel of, undated (Box 2)
    - Mark, Gospel of, undated (Box 2)
    - Luke, Gospel of, undated (Box 2)
    - John, Gospel of, undated (Box 2)
      Dr. William Hersey Davis's notes
    - John, Gospel of, 1981, 1989 (Box 2)
    - Acts, undated (Box 2)
    - Romans, 1945-1980s (Box 2)
    - I Corinthians, undated (Box 2)
    - II Corinthians, undated (Box 2)
    - Galatians, undated (Box 2)
    - Ephesians, undated (Box 2)
    - Philippians, undated (Box 2)
    - Thessalonians, undated (Box 2)
    - Philemon, undated (Box 2)
    - Hebrews, Epistle to the, 1946-1989 (Box 2)
    - James, undated (Box 2)
    - Peter, the First Epistle, undated (Box 2)
    - I, II & III John, undated (Box 2)
    - Revelation, undated (Box 2)
    - Apocrypha, undated (Box 2)
    - Deaconesses, 1980s (Box 2)
    - Holy Spirit Today, 1993 and undated (Box 2)
    - Life of Paul, undated (Box 2)
    - Parables of Jesus, 1991 (Box 2)
    - Pauline Epistles, undated (Box 2)
    - Sermon on the Mount, undated (Box 2)
    - Christian Denominations, undated (Box 2)
    - Hymn Texts: English, undated (Box 2)
    - Pedagogy, undated (Box 2)
      Handouts
    - Poetry Clippings, undated (Box 2)
    - Population Trends, 1983 (Box 2)
    - Course Evaluations, 1980s (Box 2)
      Student Course Evaluations of Carl Whirley
  - Samford University Administration, 1967-1992; 2
    - Samford University Administrative Memos, 1967-1969 (Box 2)
    - Religion Department, 1982 (Box 2)
      Department report
    - Carl Whirley Retirement Ceremony, 1986 (Box 2)
      Handouts, correspondence, programs
    - Carl Whirley Retirement Ceremony, 1986 (Box 17, Folder 2)
      Invitation
    - Directories and Admissions Information, 1979-1989 (Box 2)
      Student directories, program requirements
    - Phi Kappa Phi Fraternity Documents, 1979-1986 (Box 2)
      Correspondence, meeting minutes, memos
    - Phi Kappa Phi Fraternity Documents, 1981-1991 (Box 17, Folder 4)
      Correspondence, memos, programs
    - Samford University Missionary Apartments (SUMA), 1980s (Box 2)
      Correspondence, committee reports, notes
    - National Association of Baptist Professors of Religion, 1981-1993 and undated (Box 17, Folder 3)
      Newsletter, agendas, minutes. Some materials for the Southeast Region section.
    - Resumes and Biographies, 1982-1983 (Box 2)
    - Scholarships, 1991-1992 (Box 2)
      Scholarship application resumes
    - Truman Scholar Documents, 1980s (Box 2)
      Handout, application materials
  - Courses, 1970-1990s and undated; 3
    - Africa (Religion 498), 1980s; 2 folders (Box 3)
      Carl Whirley lecture notes, handouts, syllabi
    - Africa Today, 1967 (Box 3)
    - Africa Today (Religion 498), 1980s (Box 3)
    - Christianity in Black Africa (Religion 498), 1980s (Box 3)
      Carl Whirley lecture nores, syllabi, exams
    - Comparative Religions (Religion 301), 1980s; 2 folders (Box 3)
      Carl Whirley lecture notes, handouts, exams
    - Contemporary Ethical Issues (Philosophy/Religion 300), 1980s (Box 3)
      Carl Whirley lecture notes, exams
    - Discipleship, undated (Box 3)
      Leader materials guide
    - Elementary Greek, 1980s (Box 3)
      Handouts, syllabi, exams
    - Goal Indicators, 1987-1990 and undated; 2 folders (Box 17, Folder 6-7)
      Carl Whirley syllabi, handouts, examinations, correspondence with registrar.
    - Religion 300, Graduate Level, 1980s (Box 3)
      Handouts, syllabi
    - History of Preaching, 1970s; 3 folders (Box 3)
      Untitled book in manuscript form, outlines, Dr. Osad Imasogie papers
    - Western Civilization (History 101), 1982 (Box 3)
      Carl Whirley lecture notes, syllabus
    - Independent Studies, undated (Box 3)
      Outlines
    - Introduction to Southern Baptist Missions (200-530), 1989-1990 and undated (Box 17, Folder 8)
      Course held at New Orleans Baptist Theological Seminary. Includes correspondence, information sheet, articles of religious belief for faculty, notes for registrar, handouts.
    - Islam Today (Religion 471), 1980 (Box 3)
    - New Testament Survey (Religion 102), 1979-1986; 4 folders (Box 3)
      Carl Whirley lecture notes, handouts, syllabi, exams
    - Old Testament, 1970 (Box 3)
    - Old Testament Survey (Religion 101), 1980-1986; 3 folders (Box 3)
      Carl Whirley lecture notes, syllabi, exams, study guides
    - Other Religions and Cults (Religion 184D), 1982 (Box 4)
    - A Salute to Nigeria, 1984 (Box 17, Folder 5)
      K-6 grade. Published by the Birmingham Festival of Arts Association, Inc.
    - Student Work Samples, 1970-1983 (Box 4)
      Student essays, outlines, exams
  - Carl Whirley Coursework/Notes, 1944-1953 and undated; 4
    - Ancient Greek - Contemporary, undated (Box 4)
      Carl Whirley course notes, outlines
    - Card File for Subjects and Books (Box 19)
    - Carl Whirley Term Papers, 1945 (Box 4)
    - Christian Sociology 91, 1944-1946 (Box 4)
      Carl Whirley course notes, outlines, handouts
    - Church Administration 101, 1945 (Box 4)
      Carl Whirley course notes, untitled text in manuscript form
    - Colossians Notes, undated (Box 4)
      Carl Whirley course notes
    - Counseling, undated (Box 4)
      Manuscript text: The Pastor as a Marriage and Family Couselor by Wayne E. Oates
    - Draft Notes on Courses, undated (Box 17, Folder 9)
    - History of Interpretation, undated (Box 4)
      Untitled text in manuscript form
    - Homolectics, 1945 (Box 4)
    - Miscellaneous Course Handouts, 1951-1953 (Box 4)
    - Missions, History of (Missions 51), 1945-1946 (Box 17, Folder 10)
    - Pastorals Class, 1951 (Box 4)
    - Philippians Notes, 1947 (Box 4)
    - The Philosophy of Christian Mission, 1950-1951 (Box 4)
      Carl Whirley course notes, handouts literature
    - Program Requirements, 1950s (Box 4)
      Requirements for Graduate Study (Th.D.) in the Field of New Testament, Howard College)
    - Thesis, undated (Box 4)
      Carl Whirley thesis notes
    - Miscellaneous Notes, 1940s; 4 folders (Box 4)
- Speeches and Sermons, 1887-1994 and undated
  Speeches and Sermons contains Carl Whirley's sermon notes in both notebooks and loose-leaf papers, with handwritten and typed outlines, drafts, and notes. Also included are manuscripts of both sermons and speeches by himself and others. Arranged chronologically by year.
  - Sermon Notes, 1943-1994 and undated; 5
    - Carl Whirley Sermon Notes, 1943-1957; 13 folders (Box 4)
      Notebooks and looseleaf papers, with both handwritten and typed outlines, drafts, and notes
    - Carl Whirley Sermon Notes, 1959-1994 and undated; 40 folders (Box 5)
    - Carl Whirley Sermon Notes, undated; 3 folders (Box 6)
    - Marriage Ceremonies, undated (Box 6)
      Carl Whirley ceremony notes and outline
    - Notes Regarding Prayer, undated (Box 6)
      Sermon notes, outlines, and handouts focused on the power of prayer
  - Sermons, 1947-1990 and undated; 6
    - Sermons by Carl Whirley, 1972-1983 and undated (Box 6)
      Sermon manuscripts
    - Sermons by Carl Whirley and Others, 1980-1989 and undated (Box 17, Folder 11)
    - Sermons by Assorted Individuals, 1947-1982 (Box 6)
    - Sulligent Sermons Entertainment, 1982-1990; 3 folders (Box 17, Folder 12-14)
      Sulligent, Alabama.
    - The Healing of the Blind Man, undated (Box 6)
      Choral Drama by Agnes Durant Pylant, adapted from a dramatic sermon by Stackhouse
  - Speeches, 1887-1987 and undated; 7
    - Speech Reference File, undated (Box 17, Folder 15)
    - Speeches by Carl Whirley, 1963-1982 (Box 6)
      Speech manuscripts; often religious in topic but not delivered at church services
    - Speeches by Assorted Individuals, 1887-1987 and undated; 2 folders (Box 6)
      Speech manuscripts, cover a variety of topics, from religion, theology, and prayer to historical accounts of Nigeria
    - Southern Baptist Convention President's Addresses, 1965-1966 (Box 6)
- Correspondence, 1941-1998 and undated
  Correspondence between Carl and End Whirley with family and friends as well as various American churches and official organizations. Includes handwritten letters, typed correspondence, and emails. Official organizations include the Baptist State Executive Board, various churches in the United States, Southern Baptist Theological Seminary, Foreign Mission Board, Women's Missionary Union, and Southeastern Baptist Theological Seminary. There are also letters from Nigerians. Arranged chronologically by year.
  - Carl and Enid Whirley Correspondence, 1941-1968; 21 folders (Box 6)
    Correspondence arranged chronologically by year between Carl and Enid Whirley family, friends; Official correspondence between Whirleys and Baptist State Executive Board, Churches in the United States, Southern Baptist Theological Seminary, Foreign Mission Board, Women's Missionary Union, Southeastern Baptist Theological Seminary; 1 letter from 1981 contains photograph
  - Carl and Enid Whirley Correspondence, 1969-1993; 30 folders (Box 7)
  - Carl and Enid Whirley Correspondence, 1994-1995 and undated; 4 folders (Box 8)
  - Carl and Enid Whirley Correspondence, 1954-1998 and undated; 5 folders (Box 17, Folder 16-20)
  - Letters from Nigerians, 1966-1979 and undated; 2 folders (Box 17, Folder 21-22)
  - Address Labels, undated (Box 8)
  - Doc and Qami, undated (Box 8)
    Handwritten notes between Doc and Qami
  - Carl Whirley Personal Directory, 1993 (Box 8)
  - Samford University Correspondence, 1979-1986; 2 folders (Box 8)
    Correspondence between Carl Whirleyand Samford faculty and administration
- Nigerian Mission, 1853-1993 and undated
  Nigerian Mission includes administrative documents from official organizations and schools, group portraits, photographs of Nigerian mission buildings and personnel, materials for missionaries, and Carl and Enid Whirley's date books from the 1960s-1970s. Organizations include the American Baptist Mission, Baptist Education Board, Baptist Mission of Nigeria, Christian Workers' Board, Foreign Mission Board, Lagos Baptist Association, and the Women's Missionary Union. Schools include Baptist College, Hausa Pastor's School, Hillcrest School, Newton Memorial School, Nigerian Baptist Theological Seminary, and the Olivet Baptist High School. Missionary materials include handbooks and guides for new missionaries, hymn texts in foreign languages such as Hausa, church year guides, and church leadership information. Also included is the "Whirley Day" Scrapbook, made by the Shades Mountain Baptist Church in Alabama. It contains correspondence between the Whirleys and several American church congregations. Arranged alphabetically by folder title.
  - American Baptist Mission, 1950-1956; 2 folders (Box 8)
    Ibadan, Nigeria; Meeting minutes
  - American Baptist Mission Education Board, 1960-163 (Box 8)
    Nigeria; Meeting minutes
  - American Baptist Mission Building Administrative Committee, 1962-1963 (Box 8)
  - American Baptist Mission Finanical Documents, 1958-1963 (Box 8)
    Nigeria; Budgets and funding documents
  - Army Children's School, 1961-1962 (Box 8)
    Kaduna, Nigeria; Administrative papers and correspondence
  - Assorted Finanical Documents, 1947-1981 (Box 8)
    Budgets, receipts, and notes
  - Assorted Meeting Notes, 1966 (Box 8)
    Nigeria; Meeting notes
  - Assorted Missionary Reports, 1956-1964 (Box 8)
    Nigeria, Sierra Leone; Survery reports and outlines
  - Assorted Nigerian Missionary Campus Photographs, undated (Box 8)
    Ede, Nigeria
  - Baptist Education Board, 1962 (Box 8)
  - Baptist Hospital, 1962 (Box 8)
    Kontagora, Nigeria; Advisory board meeting minutes
  - Baptist College, undated (Box 8)
    Iwo, Nigeria; decal
  - Baptist Mission Executive Committee, 1979-1980 (Box 17, Folder 23)
  - Baptist Mission of Nigeria, 1970-1978 (Box 8)
    Nigeria; Annual meeting minutes, notes, handouts
  - The Baptist Union of Switzerland, 1970 (Box 8)
    Religious creed with scripture annotations
  - Biographies, undated (Box 8)
    Biographies of church members and missionaries
  - Candid Photographs, undated (Box 8)
    Iwo, Nigeria and other
  - Certificates, 1946-1968 (Box 8)
    Miscellaneous certificates from school children and Sunday school
  - Christian Workers' Board, 1958-1961 (Box 8)
  - Church Administration and Leadership, 1940s (Box 8)
    Manuals and guides on various roles in church leadership positions
  - Church Year, undated (Box 8)
    Church calendar and service guides
  - Committee on Condition of Service for Doctors and Dentists, 1958 (Box 8)
    Nigeria; Meeting minutes and notes
  - Carl and Enid Whirley Date Books, 1955-1977; 2 folders (Box 8)
    Date books with meetings and events notated
  - Evangelical Evaluation, 1974 (Box 9)
    Lusaka, Zambia; Conference handouts
  - Exercepts from Untitled Publication, undated (Box 9)
    Photographs of Nigerian mission
  - Foreign Hymn Texts, undated (Box 9)
    Hymn texts in foreign languages, including Hausa
  - Foreign Mission Board, 1971-1981 (Box 9)
    Eku, Nigeria and other; Administrative documents, search committees, meeting minutes
  - Foreign Mission Board of the Southern Baptist Convention, 1979-1982 (Box 9)
    Form letters, administrative forms, handouts
  - Foundation Laying at Ede Baptist High School, 1968 (Box 9)
    Photographs of Carl Whirley at foundation laying, correspondence included
  - Group Portraits, undated (Box 9)
    Group portraits of Nigerian missionaries and church members
  - Hausa Pastor's School, 1961 (Box 9)
    Nigeria; Staff meeting minutes
  - Hillcrest School, 1961-1971 (Box 9)
    Jos, Nigeria; Letters to parents, meeting minutes
  - Information for New Missionaries, 1947, 1952 (Box 9)
    Handouts and guidelines for new missionaries
  - Intermediate Book, 1967 (Box 9)
    Manuscript textbook by Carl Whirley
  - Lagos Baptist Association, 1964 and undated (Box 9)
    Directory and Lagos postcard
  - A Listing of Missionaries by Country, 1979 (Box 9)
    Pamphlet listing international missionaries
  - Maguire Missionary Scholarship, 1990 and undated (Box 17, Folder 24)
  - Maps and Posters, 1971 and undated (Box 9)
    Map of Southern Baptist Missions in Africa; Poster for Week of Christian Prayer in Nigeria; Poster for Women's Missionary Union Golden Jubilee Fundraising (Ibadan, Nigeria)
  - Mission Executive Committee, 1963 (Box 9)
    Ogbomosho, Nigeria; Meeting minutes
  - Missionary Evangelism, 1952-1964 (Box 9)
  - Missionary Orientation Group Photograph, 1950s (Box 9)
    Richmond, Virginia
  - Missionary Account and Travel Log, 1853-1856 (Box 9)
    Lagos, Nigeria
  - Missionaries Reunion, 1993 (Box 9)
    Directory
  - Namecard Ephemera, undated (Box 9)
    Carl and Enid Whirley namecards
  - Newton Memorial School, 1961-1966 (Box 9)
    Osogbo, Nigeria; Letters to parents, administrative documents, yearbook
  - Nigeria-Alabama Partnership in Mission, 1983-1984 (Box 17, Folder 25)
  - Nigerian Baptist Convention Minutes, 1914-1979 (Box 9)
  - Nigerian Baptist Convention Administration, 1962 (Box 9)
    Administrative documents and correspondence
  - Nigerian Baptist Theological Seminary, 1980 and undated (Box 17, Folder 26)
  - Nigerian Baptist Theological Seminary Administration, 1966-1978; 2 folders (Box 9)
    Ogbomosho, Nigeria; Administrative documents, faculty meeting minutes, calendars
  - Nigerian Baptist Theological Seminary Annual Candidate Report, 1980 (Box 9)
    Ogbomosho, Nigeria
  - Nigerian Baptist Theological Seminary Board of Governors, 1979-1981; 2 folders (Box 9)
  - Nigerian Baptist Theological Seminary Student Handbooks, 1967, 1977 (Box 9)
  - Nigerian Baptist Theological Seminary Institutional Self Study, 1988 (Box 9)
  - Nigerian Baptist Theological Seminary Outline, 1966 (Box 9)
    Ogbomosho, Nigeria; Outline of Nigerian history
  - Nigerian Baptist Theological Seminary Whirley Retirement Materials, 1979 (Box 17, Folder 27)
  - Nigerian Baptist Theological Seminary Worship, 1970-1972 (Box 9)
    School worship handouts
  - Nigerian Mission Planning, 1947-1951 (Box 9)
    Financial documents and outlines